empire.kred 2018-06-29

# Empire.Kred - Grow your Social Audience

## Privacy Policy

_This document updated: 19/04/2011_

#### Empire Kred Pty Ltd. (Empire.Kred) considers issues relating to your privacy to be a serious matter. As such, Empire.Kred has created and implemented this Privacy Policy so that you understand what Empire.Kred may and may not do with certain Personal Information. 

#### This Privacy Policy describes the guidelines Empire Avenue uses to protect the information we collect about you during your visit(s) to the Empire.Kred Web site ( the “Web Site”). By registering on the Web Site you consent to the collection and use of information described below and in the Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use. 

#### This Privacy Policy will apply to all websites of Empire Avenue that link to this Privacy Policy. Information will be shared with other users in accordance with this Policy and your Privacy Settings. You are encouraged to review your Privacy Settings on a regular basis to ensure the levels are set appropriately. 

### Collection of Information

Empire.Kred will collect information of three types about you: (1) Personal Information, (2) Web Site Information, and (3) Third Party Information.

  1. Personal Information refers to information that you provide us directly (i.e. through the forms on the site). This includes but is not limited to your name, photo, your date of birth, your e-mail address, your country, your interests, your profile information etc. 
  2. Web Site Information is information that Empire.Kred collects about you during use of the Website. This can be information obtained from posts on your profile pages, your private messaging, and other account activity. It may also be collected about you from the messages and posts and account activity of others regarding you. It also includes information like your browser type and IP address. We may use "cookies" to help us store and collect other information based on your browsing.[1]
  3. When you register as a Registered User, Empire.Kred will enable you to provide us with your login information for various third party sites (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Flickr and your Blog site). Empire.Kred will then access your account and gather all necessary information from these third party sites as dictated by your Privacy Settings on those sites and as required in providing scores, recommendations and share prices. This information is called Third Party Information. We will remove this Third Party Information from our system after a certain period of time (currently set at a month). 

The information set out in subparagraphs (2) and (3) above will be gathered by an automated system and will not be available in its original format unless you have given us explicit permission via your Privacy Settings. 

### Children Under Age 13

Empire.Kred does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register with Empire.Kred or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete any personal information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@empire.kred](mailto:info@empire.kred)

### Internal Use of Information 

When you use Empire.Kred, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as Personal Information, comments, messages, photos, videos, or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the Privacy Settings you select. Information regarding your network scores and your Empire.Kred virtual stock price may be shared and searchable through your public profile to services and users outside of Empire.Kred. However, the information available on your Empire.Kred public profile can be controlled, or the profile disabled, in your personal Privacy Settings.

In addition to this, Empire.Kred reserves the right to access, utilize, and reproduce personal information it collects about you, though it will obey any restrictions set up in your Privacy Settings. 

We may use your name and contact information to send you notifications regarding changes to our service or new services offered by Empire.Kred that we think you may find valuable.

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will send your friend an email or instant message in your name inviting him or her to visit the site, and may send up to two reminders to them. Empire.Kred stores this information to send invitations and reminders.

### Sharing of Information with Third Parties 

Empire.Kred engages certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services including, without limitation, hosting, maintenance, and database storage and management, Empire.Kred will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Empire.Kred business, or individual business units owned by Empire.Kred, were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. 

### Links 

The Web Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Empire.Kred.

### Changing or Removing Information 

Access and control over your personal information on the Web Site is readily available to you through the profile editing tools. Empire.Kred users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Empire.Kred account may do soon the Settings pages. Removed Personal Information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of Empire.Kred. It may also remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content. 

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on the Web Site, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another Web Site user) you generally cannot remove such communications.

### Security 

Empire.Kred takes appropriate precautions to protect the Information of all of our users. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. If you have any questions about the security of the Empire.Kred Web Site, please contact us through the [Help Centre](mailto:support@empiravenue.com). 

### Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions 

Your use of Empire.Kred, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

### Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may also contact us at [privacy@empireavenue.com](mailto:privacy@empireavenue.com). 

_This document updated: 19/04/2011_

* * *

[1]A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Empire.Kred. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.
